http://www.icewarp.com/privacy/

Education
We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. You consent to our cookies if you continue to use our website. (learn more)
Continue
PRIVACY POLICY
IntroductionIceWarp, Inc. considers the responsible collection, use and confidentiality of collected personal data to be of the utmost importance in enabling the Internet to reach its full potential. We consider personal data that is collected via www.icewarp.com to be the ownership of the users that submit the information and NOT our own. At the same time, we believe privacy and trust to be the cornerstone of our operating philosophy. Therefore, our goal is to work to combine the best of Internet technology with personal privacy to deliver content, services and information of interest to each user.Commitment to PrivacyThe privacy of each user is of primary importance to us. To better provide privacy protections, IceWarp, Inc. is providing this notice to explain our online information practices regarding the way your information is collected and used.Personal InformationMost of the services provided by www.icewarp.com can be used without the need for collection of personal information of any kind. There are times, however, when we may need information from web site users. Personal information (such as name, address and e-mail address for example) are obtained only when voluntarily submitted, such as when a user subscribes to a newsletter, responds to a user survey, registers for programs / events / licensed software, or purchases a product through our e-commerce solution.How We Use the Information We CollectWe intend to let each and every user, who chooses to provide personal information to our services via the Internet, know exactly how their information will be used at the time they provide it. As mentioned above, we typically use personal information to fulfill subscription requests, orders, provide access to online services, etc.We may also use the information that users supply to:- make the service easier to use by not having to enter information more than once- help us customize content most relevant to users- notify users about important news and special offers that they may be interested in (with their permission)In the process of administering our site, we maintain and track usage through web server logs. Web server logs provide such information as what types of browsers are accessing our site, what pages receive high traffic, and the times of day our servers experience significant load. We use this information to improve the content and navigation features of our site. It is not used to attempt to identify individual users in any way, but to ensure our sites are designed and responding effectively to the requirements of each users.How We Share InformationThree words … „we do not“. IceWarp, Inc. will not sell, rent, lease, give or barter personally identifiable information collected through our services to any third party directly or indirectly without your express permission.ConsentIceWarp, Inc. will only use and share the personally identifiable information users provide in ways related to those described above. We reserve the right to disclose any and all pertinent customer information to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. (Example: threatening the well being of another person or entity through the use of a IceWarp, Inc. built system.)Our Commitment to Data SecurityIceWarp, Inc. is concerned about the security of information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use encryption technology when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information.CookiesCookies can be used to provide tailored information to a return visitor to a Web site. Cookies do not damage files or allow anyone to access your personally identifiable information – they simply allow us to tailor information and make your visits more enjoyable, efficient and useful. We may share aggregate (never individual) site usage statistics and but this information will NEVER include any personally identifiable information. (Example: Total number of hits over a certain time period, total number of page views per page, total number of users from a specific region.)There are two types of cookies in use today, persistent and non-persistent cookies. „Persistent Cookies“ are stored between sessions on a computer's hard drive and thus are physically written to the drive, whereas „Non-Persistent Cookies“ reside in the memory of the users' machine and expire when the browser is closed. For purely usability and scalability reasons, IceWarp, Inc. sometimes uses either persistent or non-persistent cookies.Some IceWarp, Inc.-based developed services use cookies or other technologies so that we can better serve Web site users when they return to a site. We do not use cookies or similar technology to cross-relate personal information about visitors. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. For more information, please refer to user information provided by your specific Web browser.IP AddressesIceWarp, Inc. uses IP addresses (static or random numbers assigned to individual computers) to help diagnose problems with our servers, administer our web site, and anonymously track content preferences and traffic patterns. IP addresses are also recorded in e-commerce type transactions to provide a point of reference in situations where credit card fraud has occurred.WebClient TelemetryYou agree that IceWarp may use anonymous usage statistics collected through WebClient telemetry. IceWarp may use this information, as long as it is in an aggregated form that does not personally identify you or any of your users, to improve and develop our products. You can opt out from providing telemetry data during the installation or upgrade. No data will be collected until the consent is accepted again on the next installation.
Show me IceWarp
Company
Select your Country
Afghanistan
Albania
Algeria
American Samoa
Andorra
Cote D`Ivoire (Ivory Coast)
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands (U.S.)
Cote D`Ivoire (Ivory Coast)
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands (U.S.)
When should we call you?
Error checking CAPTCHA. Please, try again one more time.
Error sending form. Please, try again one more time.
Cote D`Ivoire (Ivory Coast)
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands (U.S.)
Cote D`Ivoire (Ivory Coast)
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands (U.S.)
How can we help you?
I don't wish to receive any marketing communication
Error checking CAPTCHA. Please, try again one more time.
Error sending form. Please, try again one more time.
Sorry, this message looks like a spam message.
'Message' field can not contain URLs.
Send
